人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：小萌        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十二集
看哎  看哎
Lookie, lookie.
我在圣巴特里克节那天当陪审员时穿的
My green blazer from when I had
绿色西装
jury duty on Saint Patrick's Day.
纪念爱尔兰守护神圣巴特里克的节日
庆祝方式之一是穿戴绿色服装
找出这件西装干什么
What's the blazer for?
蒂娜要穿着它参加明天
Tina's gonna wear it at her audition tomorrow
学校新闻台的面试
for the school news channel.
我想当一名严肃的女主播
I want to be serious newswoman,
美国电影  主人公是一位
叫霍利・亨特的新闻节目制作人
就像《广播新闻》中的霍利・享特一样
like Holly Hunter in Broadcast News.
"永远正确一定很棒
"It must be great being right all the time.
不  这很糟"
No, it's terrible."
我需要练习怎么做电视记者
I need to practice being a television journalist.
老爸  我能采访你吗
Dad, can I interview you?
好吧
Um, okay.
不要直视摄像机  老爸
Don't look directly into the camera, Dad.
知道了
I got it.
那么请问  为什么要开汉堡店
So, tell me, why burgers?
我是在父亲的鼓励下开起来的
Well, my dad got me started...
你是否将此视为
Do you see this as a stepping stone
开一家真正餐馆的跳板
to a real restaurant?
我现在开的就是真正的餐馆
It... is a real restaurant.
二流饭店
Mm, slop shop.
除了汉堡你还会烹饪其它菜品吗
Can you cook anything other than burgers?
是的  还会很多东西
Yes, lots of things.
-比如说  -例如
- Like? - Like, um...
比如  西班牙海鲜饭
like, paella.
西班牙海鲜饭  给我讲讲那怎么做
Paella-- tell me how you make that.
我得看一眼食谱  但是
Well, I'd have to look up the recipe, but, uh...
这么说你不会西班牙海鲜饭了
So you don't know how to make paella?
不  我能做
No, I could make...
这我就不懂了  一分钟之前
Okay, I'm confused, because a minute ago
你明明还是副专家的模样
you were an expert.
老爸需要传媒形象指导
Dad needs media coaching.
听着  西班牙海鲜饭是我随口说的
Look, I randomly said "Paella."
我没想那么多
I didn't mean to.
来点特写
Ah, I'm going in tight.
鲍勃  别再提西班牙海鲜饭了
Bob, get off paella.
够了  采访结束了
All right, interview's over.
把摄像机从我面前拿开
Get that camera out of my face.
我想我们的新闻素材已经够了
I think we got what we need.
你看起来棒极了  亲爱的
You look amazing, sweetie.
在摄像机里看起来肯定会更好
And you're gonna look even better on camera.
你继承了我硬朗的下巴
You inherited my strong chin.
你硬朗的下巴在哪儿  老妈
Where's your strong chin, Mom?
我怎么看不到
I can't see it.
继续看  你会找到的
Keep looking, you'll find it.
我从你那里继承了什么  老妈
What did I inherit from you, Mom?
你继承了我对生活的热枕之心
You got my zest for life.
还有我格外长的粉色脚趾
And my extra long pinky toe.
我继承了你能生的屁股
And I got your birthing hips.
事实上  吉恩  你更像你父亲
Actually, Gene, you take more after your father.
不对  屁股是不会撒谎的
No, hips don't lie.
歌曲名  由夏奇拉演唱
看这个
Look at this.
忘了我还有长的像贾德・纳尔逊的阶段了
I forgot that I went through a Judd Nelson phase.
美国演员  剧作家  制作人
那是你父亲和你一般大的时候
That's your father when he was your age.
看起来和你一模一样
He looked just like you.
等等  你的意思是等我到他的年龄时
Wait, does that mean when I'm his age,
我也会长成他那样么
I'm gonna look just like him?
剧透慎入哦
Spoiler alert!
不
No!
长这样已经算不错了好吧
Hey, you could do worse.
我怎么没看出来
I don't see how!
至少你知道你的肩膀不会光秃秃的
At least you know your shoulders won't go bald.
吉恩  已经开始了
Gene, it's starting.
我在你的枕头上发现了这个
I found this on your pillow!
天哪
Ah! Oh, my God!
快  快帮我拨一拨  帮我遮起来
Quick, come me over! Trump me!
-露易丝  -怎么了
- Louise... - What?
你不会秃头的  吉恩
You're not going bald, Gene.
快道歉  露易丝
Apologize, Louise.
对不起  对不起  对不起
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
如果我命中注定会变成那样
What's the point of clinging to this,
执着于此又有什么用处
if I'm doomed to be that?
-说得也是哦  -琳
- Huh. I don't know. - Lin.
还等什么  现在就来吧
Why wait? Let's do it now.
让我完全变成鲍勃那样吧
I want the whole Bob.
男性斑秃
Male-pattern baldness.
-下垂的肩膀  -别说了
- Stoop shoulders. - Stop.
-啤酒肚  -求你了
- Paunch. - Please.
嘴唇上方再来个扫把
And the push broom on my lip.
这真是十足的侮辱
This is incredibly insulting.
想想我的感受吧
Think about how I feel.
你怎么能让我任其发展
You really let myself go.
去上学
Go to school.
-我们走了  -再见
- We're going. - Bye.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
记住  孩子们
Remember, kids,
这只是学生新闻 不要有压力
this is just the student news, no pressure.
我只是会逐帧回顾
I'll only be going back frame by frame
评判你们的眼神交流
and critiquing you on eye contact,
新闻陈述  以及长相
presentation and how cool you are.
你确定要参加吗
You really want to do this?
好了  第一个上场的到绿屏幕那里
Okay, first up to the green screen,
体育新闻播报  齐克
Zeke with sports.
我来啦  格兰特老师
Comin' at ya, Mr. Grant!
这场比赛十分激烈  过程相当白热化
That game was tighter than a tater in a tailpipe.
就像是两个婴儿爬上同一个胸部
It was like two babies climbin' on the same boob.
然后我们输了
Then we lost.
齐克  我好像身临其境
Wow, Zeke, I feel like I was there.
下一个  应聘的是现场记者
Next up, auditioning for field reporters,
安迪和奥利
Andy and Ollie.
话筒交还给你  安迪
Back to you, Andy.
交还给你  奥利
Back to you, Ollie.
交还给你  安迪
Back to you, Andy.
交还给你  奥利
Back to you, Ollie.
要是你们俩是连体婴就好了
If only you two were Siamese twins.
我们可以的
We can do that.
太棒了
Oh, great!
如果你们能做到可就帮大忙了
That'd be super helpful if you could figure that out.
看来好像成功了
It looks like it's working.
我们成功了
We did it!
太好了
So sweet.
下一位是应聘竞争激烈的主播一职的苔米
And, next up, for the coveted anchor spot, Tammy.
祝你好运  苔米
Good luck, Tammy.
我天生就有好运  蒂娜
Uh, I was born lucky, Tina.
因为我是我  而不是你
'Cause I was born me and not you.
我现在又是金发  所以肯定比你强
And I'm a blonde now, so I'm better than you.
我不喜欢你的说法
I don't like what you say,
但是我很羡慕你能那么说话
but I admire the way you say it.
这是苔米为您献上的新闻
Wow, it's Tammy with the news!
新  闻
Whoo! News...
新闻
News.
苔  很棒  多谢  小姐
Tam, slam, thank you, ma'am.
下一个  蒂娜
Next up, Tina.
蒂娜  小决窍
Oh, hey, Tina, little tip:
你说话实在太快了  所以你应该慢点说
you're a super fast talker, so talk really slow.
多谢  苔米
Thanks, Tammy.
还是太快了
That's still way too fast.
格兰特老师
Mr. Grant,
我来这里是因为我对新闻有着敏锐的直觉
I'm here because I have a nose for news.
很好  不过关于那件绿色的夹克
Great. Now about that green jacket...
我是蒂娜
I'm Tina with...
蒂娜
Tina.
带  来
...with... the...
见鬼啦
Paranormal activity!
瓦格斯塔夫小学新闻小组
天哪  我是主播了  好耶  好耶
Oh, my God, I'm anchor! Yes! Yes!
我是主播了
I am anchor!
我是实习员工
I'm staff intern?
但是我都想好结束语了
But I already had a sign-off.
"再见了  观众们"
"Good-bye, audience."
也许你可以换成
Well, maybe you could change it to
"有人需要果汁吗"
"Does anyone need juice?"
有人需要果汁吗
Does anyone need juice?
要是你买到了果汁效果会更好
Hmm. Maybe it'll work better when you have some juice.
实习员工都做些什么
So, what does the staff intern do?
除了跑腿买果汁外吗
Besides go on juice box runs?
-是的  -有很多事情可做
- Yeah. - Oh, lots of things.
分发果汁
You know, hand out the juice,
确保大家都喝得高兴
make sure people are happy with their juice,
清理所有空果汁盒
clean up all the empty juice boxes.
好吧  还有其它重要的幕后工作
Okay. Isn't there any other important
是我可以帮上忙的吗
behind-the-scenes stuff I could do to help?
还有编辑音乐和音效的工作
Well, there's editing music, effects.
-这可是很酷的差事  -太好了
- That stuff is a blast. - Great.
但这是我负责的
But I do those.
如果你都做了  那要我干什么
I mean, if you did them, what would I do?
当老师
Be the teacher?
是啊  蒂娜  当老师最好了
Yeah, right, Tina, that sounds great.
我教书就好了
I'll just teach.
头顶剪一点
Little more off the top.
后面和耳边都撒点
Sprinkle on the back and the ears.
再来点胶水
A little more glue.
让我看看  让我看看
Show me, show me!
太完美了
It's perfect!
我变成黑黢黢的鲍勃了
I've been tarred and Bobbed.
我本不知道要怎么让臂毛的长相
I don't know how I got that arm hair
看上去可怜一点  但我做到了
to look so sad, but I did it.
能进来吗  我得...
Can I get in here? I need to...
天哪
Oh, my God!
好像是在照镜子
It's like looking in a mirror!
-不  才不像  吉恩  -吉恩是谁
- No, it isn't, Gene. - Who's Gene?
我已经分不清谁是谁了
I already can't tell who's who.
把那东西拿下来
Take that stuff off.
琳  快过来调解一下
Lin, get in here and settle this!
别对你妈直呼其名
Don't call your mother Lin.
怎么了
What? Oh!
怎么  缩小版的鲍勃诶
Wha... h-hey! Whoa, travel-size Bob.
琳达  你这是在纵容他
Linda, you're encouraging him.
我想上厕所
I need the bathroom.
我都迷乎了
Oh. Wow, this is confusing.
不  不能够
No, it's not.
你们是我的家人  我爱你们
You're my family and I love you,
但你们太逊了  你们都太逊了
but you're terrible. You're all terrible.
-我可不那么说话  -你一直这么说话
- I don't say that. - Well, that's all you say.
-是的  -你是这么说话
- You do. - You kind of do.
真不敢相信
Unbelievable.
-吉恩  -鲍勃
- Gene. - Bob.
-好了  够了  -够了
- All right, enough. - Enough.
-我不要跟你玩这个  -是的  你要
- I'm not doing this. - Yes, you are.
-不  我  天哪  -天哪
- No, I'm... oh, my God. - Oh, God.
他演得真像  他真棒
He's really good. He's good.
他才不棒  琳
He's not good, Lin.
他很棒
He's good.
-吉恩  -怎么  鲍勃
- Gene! - What, Bob?!
-琳  -琳
- Lin! - Lin!
-咋了  -吉恩
- What? - Gene!
-琳  -琳
- Lin! - Lin!
吉恩  我走了
Gene! I'm leaving!
他太可爱了
Aw, he's so cute.
别跟着我
Stop following me!
别在前面跟着我
Stop following me in front!
你好  布兰卡先生
Hi, Mr. Branca.
当心  蒂娜  很滑
Careful, Tina. Slippery.
波斯基夫人的羊水破了吗
Did Mrs. Persky's water break?
这是羊水吗
I may have won the baby pool.
比这个更糟  有人带了狗屎进来
Worse. Someone dragged in a dog turd.
这也不是第一次了
And this isn't the first time, either.
你总有很棒的故事  布兰卡先生
You have great stories, Mr. Branca.
我有没有说过你很像我最好的好朋友
I ever tell you you're, like, my best friend?
谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
这档新闻节目旨在将学生们的注意力
Look, this news show competes for students' attention
从手机  八卦和厕所涂鸦中转移出来
with cell phones, gossip and bathroom graffiti.
我们要更快  更贱  更恶俗
We need to be faster, meaner, and graffiti-er!
因此  我...
So, what I'm...
一盒酸果蔓苹果味的  两盒葡萄味的
I have a cran-apple, two grapes
剩下的都是奇异果草莓味的
and a bunch of kiwi-strawberry.
这盒有你要的螺旋吸管  齐克
Here's the crazy straw you asked for, Zeke.
按照你的要求  额外加了螺旋
Extra crazy, just how you like it.
可以再多加几圈
Could be crazier.
好了  校园新闻的五要素是
Now, who knows the five W's of school news?
"人物  事件  地点
Oh, "Who, what, where,
时间  偶尔还有原因"
when and sometimes why."
有原因这一项么
Or, is that vowels?
不不
No!
是 "赞  好耶  劲爆
They're "Wow, woo-hoo,
奇葩  不了个是吧"
way hot, weird and what the mmm."
每一条我们都要做到上述五点
Every story we do should have all five.
我有一条
I've got one,
新生走光照片
new kid nip slips!
够劲爆  齐克
Way hot, Zeke!
谁家是穷光蛋
Oh, whose parents are poor?
好耶  苔米
Woo-hoo, Tammy!
我有一条
I've got one.
看门大爷说有人在带狗屎进学校
The custodian says someone is tracking in dog poo.
这有爆点吧
What the huh?
要疯癫  不要便便  蒂娜
Less caca, more gaga, Tina.
其他人呢
Anyone else?
我听说四年级有个45岁胡须男
I hear there's a 45-year-old fourth grader
在学校四处溜达
with a mustache walking around school.
这个才真是很有爆点
Now that's pretty "What the ah"!
就用那个
Go with that.
瓦格斯塔夫小学新闻
这里是瓦格斯塔夫小学新闻时间
This is WSN, the news you need
由人气主播为你播报你最感兴趣的新闻
from the students you like.
给你好"看"
In your face!
我是苔米・拉森  今天的重大新闻有
I'm Tammy Larson and these are the breaking stories.
布伦达这是怎么了
What's up with Brenda?
大家都懂吧
I mean, right?
小吉米・派丝多编排了一出舞蹈
Jimmy Pesto Junior previews dance moves
而校长禁止其在冬季舞会表演
the principal won't allow at winter prom.
髋要拱出来
This one's out.
做不到吧
Can't do this.
忘了还有这个动作
Forget about this one.
我爱这个调调  可这并不是新闻
I love it, but it's not news.
下面是我们的头条新闻
Now, to our top story:
连尼・戴斯特法诺  人气校草众女争抢
Lenny Destefano-- is there enough of him to go around,
王子分身乏术  姑娘们爱意难抑
and how can we ration our passion?
乔丝玲  连尼冬季舞会的舞伴是谁啊
Jocelyn, who's Lenny going to the winter prom with?
没人知道  他正和朱莉约会
No one knows. He's going out with Julie,
可一直和整个啦啦队的妞们包括我发短信
but he's been texting the entire drill team and me.
-当然还有我  -天啊
- And me, also. - Oh.
下面由齐克带我们欣赏躲避球的精彩瞬间
Now to Zeke with dodgeball highlights.
谢了  苔米
Thanks, Tammy!
有人被击中"小弟弟"
Here's a kid getting it in the muchachos.
这人的彩"蛋"也吃了一记
Here's another dude, right in the Easter eggs.
来看这个一字胡老头中招
Watch this geezer with a 'stache get his.
打中也不要紧  我早儿孙满堂了
It's okay, I've had my kids.
蒂娜  我看过新闻了
Hey, Tina, I saw the news.
连尼和啦啦队的事是真的吗
Is that true about Lenny and the drill team?
朱莉这朵花算是插牛粪上了
Julie deserves better.
学校这锅汤才是被新闻这颗屎毁了
The school deserves better news.
我刚从图书馆回来
Well, I just got back from the library.
那儿踩屎的鞋印更多了
More shoe poopy got dragged in up there.
往资料室那儿拖了一路
All the way to the reference section.
美国少儿读物
此处Encyclopedia[百科全书]指事故发生地图书馆
而Brown[棕色]则暗指大便
这不是《数学小神探》嘛
Talk about Encyclopedia Brown.
我  我没听懂
I... I don't get it.
等等
Wait,
踩屎的鞋印能走那么远吗
that's a pretty long way to track something in on a shoe.
我要调查一下
I'm gonna poke around.
什么味道不太对
Something doesn't smell right.
这个吧
That's this.
是它
Oh, yeah.
所以就是苹果酱了  可要是去
So it is applesauce, but try to find it
超市果酱货架找一瓶对比
in the sauce aisle at the supermarket.
你会非常失望
You'll be sorely disappointed.
这个先不提  我当时在找酸辣酱
Anyway, I was looking for chutney.
这故事很长吗  泰迪
Uh, is this a long story, Teddy?
现在已经很长了  还要更长吗
I mean, it has been long, but is it longer?
我还没说到故事的部分
I haven't gotten to the story part yet.
吉恩  你站柜台后面来
Gene, I need you behind the counter.
就站这儿  我去去就回
Just stand here and I'll be right back.
我不喜欢你用这样的办法
I'm not sure I appreciate
来敷衍我  鲍勃
being foisted off like this, Bob.
所以  我就到了民族风味食品区了
So, anyway, I end up in the ethnic food section.
好像打开了通往新世界的门
It was like a whole new world opened up.
我买了印度产的婴儿食品
I bought baby food from India.
喝这个的婴儿着实强悍
Those babies are tough.
那些"薄"片真不是开玩笑的
No joke on those slices.
你讲得太棒了  泰迪
That's fascinating, Teddy.
小鲍勃也很棒
Little Bob is great.
是啊  我看可以让他保持这个模样
Yeah, I guess I'll keep him.
琳  打住
Lin, stop.
-你才打住  -不  够了  琳
- You stop. - No, stop, Lin.
不  你打住  小鲍鲍
No, you stop, little Bobby.
-打住吧  -鲍鲍  打住
- Mm-hmm, stop. - Bobby, stop.
看看你俩  就像结婚多年的老夫妻一样
Look at you two, you're like an old married couple.
我们相互容忍彼此
We put up with each other.
好了  够了  吉恩
All right, enough, Gene.
吉恩  回厨房来
Gene, get back to the kitchen.
踩狗屎的鞋印怎么能一路
How could dog poop make it all the way
上两层楼梯还进入图书馆
up two flights of stairs and into the library
屎印却不见消失呢
on a shoe without being wiped off?
移"屎"换影么
Tele-poop-tation?
试验看看吧
Let's experiment.
我们需要一个
We need something
和屎大小及材质一样的东西
the exact same size and texture as poop.
老爸的汉堡怎么样
How about Dad's burger?
颜色都一样了
It's even the same color!
好主意
Great idea.
你俩究竟干嘛呢
What the hell are you kids doing?
踩着老爸的汉堡走路
Walking on one of Dad's burgers
看看它和狗屎有多像
to see how much like dog doo it is.
科学实验
Oh, science.
很干净
It's clean.
那只能说明一件事
That can mean only one thing:
屎源一定在学校内部
the poos must have come from inside the school.
也就是说  可能是人屎
Which means, they're probably human!
我知道新闻要讲什么了
I knew there was a story there.
我们处理的是一起连环纵屎案
We're looking at a serial pooper.
我的天
Oh, my God.
是你吗  露易丝
Is it you, Louise?
我倒是有心尝试呢
I've dabbled in the area,
可我有限的饭量导致我没有足够的屎源
but I don't get enough food to be a serial pooper.
我一周可能只有一坨屎
I, uh, probably only poop once a week.
我想为犯人取代号为变态屎犯
I think I'll call the culprit the Mad Pooper.
我有个更好的
Ooh, I got a better one.
屎男仆  有没有
The Butt-ler. Get it?
buttler意为管家或男仆
其中含有butt即屁股一词
我懂了  把屁股藏在词里了
I get it. It's got "Butt" in it.
屁股
Butt.
不管叫什么吧  这无疑是条新闻
Whatever we call him or her, it's definitely news.
那是厕所新闻  蒂娜
That's toilet journalism, Tina.
我们做的是低级趣味新闻
We do gutter journalism.
可现在学校有个变态屎犯在作案
But there's a Mad Pooper loose in the school.
向大众公布真相是新闻的职责
It's the job of the news to inform the public.
就算只能挽救一只鞋  也值得
It's worth it, even if we save just one shoe.
真恶心
Yuck.
说得好  苔米
Well said, Tammy.
变态屎犯的事比连尼・戴斯特法诺的
The Mad Pooper story is ten times bigger
感情生活重要十倍
than Lenny Destefano's love life.
而且还没那么恶心
And less disgusting.
他会把嘴唇放到一切能啵啵的东西上
He'll put his lips on anything with pom-poms.
但这事他们不让我播
But I can't get it out there.
瓦格斯塔夫小学新闻很垄断
WSN has a news monopoly.
那做你自己的新闻节目吧
So do your own newscast.
我自己的新闻节目
My own newscast?
你觉得我做得来吗
You think I could do that?
是谁总嚷嚷自己鼻子有灵敏的新闻嗅觉的
Who's the one yammering about her nose for news?
我吗
Me?
对  就是这只鼻子
Yeah, this nose right here!
使劲闻闻  嗅点新闻线索出来啊
Get it sniffing! Snort some news up there!
我嗅不了  你捏着我的鼻子呢
I can't snort 'cause you're holding my nose.
还会有很多事阻挡你的脚步
There's gonna be lots of things holding you back!
好吧
Okay.
嗅起来
Snort it up!
来啊  克朗凯特  嗅起来
Come on, Cronkite, snort!
美国传奇新闻主播沃尔特・克朗凯特
这是给大家造福呢
It's for the good of the people!
你有线索了立马告诉我
Let me know when you got something.
我的透视模型  被透"屎"了
My diorama... got diarrheaed.
我想我刚刚嗅到一丝线索了
I think I just snorted a story.
老爸的旧摄影机  磁带和录像带各一盒
Dad's old camcorder, a VCR and a videotape?
向最顶尖的摄影棚问好吧
Say hello to your state-of-the-art studio.
可  这是吉恩出生时录的啊
But, this is Gene's birth.
有很多伟大的时刻
There's a lot of crowning stuff
是只能被抹去的
that can just be taped over.
像是愤怒的垒球
Looks like an angry softball
努力从零钱袋里挣脱出来的时刻
trying to get out of a coin purse.
好啦
Hmm, okay.
听好  我的公主们
Listen, princess,
我不知道你们在讨论什么
I don't even know what you're talking about,
但你们下定决心就去做吧
but you can do anything you set your mind to.
还有  无论如何
And, no matter what,
你妈妈和我都爱你们
your mother and I will always love you.
他演得真不错
He's good.
完全再现了嗦臭屁的老爸样
That kid just fathered the crap out of you.
他是还...不错
He did... okay.
当然不错
I did great.
话多了点
Little preachy.
你光芒四射  蒂娜
You got a lot of shine on you, Tina.
你是怎么争取到校园广播网的相同时段的
How did you get equal time on the school network?
我跟校长说我有一些他的犯罪图片
I told Principal Spoors I had incriminating pictures of him.
因为我画了几张他的犯罪图片
Because I drew some incriminating pictures of him.
好极了  我们开工吧
Great, let's do this.
蒂娜新闻时间
瓦格斯塔夫小学遭遇危机
罪魁祸首"变态屎者"
此时大厅十分安静
These halls are calm now.
但就在周三  情形则截然不同
But on Wednesday, it was a different story.
我离开我的鞋盒透视模型没一会
I left my shoebox diorama for a minute
就有人往上泼了屎
and someone pooped in it.
我做的是有关工业革命的模型
It was about the Industrial Revolution.
有人称他为变态屎者
Some call him the Mad Pooper.
我妈叫她"屎男仆"
My mom calls him the Butt-ler.
无论名字如何
By any name,
每一个棕色标记都诉说着一个惊悚瞬间
these brown thumbtacks tell a tale of terror.
抱歉  我能去护士办公室
Excuse me, can I go get my medicine
拿下药么
at the nurse's office?
嘘  我正看这个呢
Shh. I'm watching this.
不是吧
Oh. Oh, no.
谁会做出这种事呢
Who would do such a thing?
我们询问了相关专家  福旺德老师
We turn to an expert, Mr. Frond.
罪犯是想借此与外界沟通
It's someone trying to communicate.
很有可能是交换留学生
Likely, a foreign- exchange student.
他心中郁积着
He or she has something inside them
拼命想要发泄出来的东西
they desperately want to get out.
-愤怒么  -便便
- Rage? - Poo.
瓦格斯塔夫学生对此怎么看
And what do Wagstaff students think?
我要对变态屎者说
My message to the Mad Pooper is:
成熟点吧  我就变成熟了
Grow up! I did.
无论变态屎犯是谁
Whoever the Mad Pooper is, he or she
他很有可能不会就此罢休
is probably not finished.
屎犯不落网  我也就不会放弃
And if they're not, I'm not.
我是蒂娜・贝尔彻  在大厅为您报道
In the hall, I'm Tina Belcher.
收工
And we're clear.
是的  我做到了
Yes, I did it.
接招吧  苔米
Take that, Tammy.
还有霍利・亨特
And Holly Hunter.
我错了  还没结束
I lied, we're not clear.
好了  现在结束了
Okay, now we're clear.
我会把刚才那段剪了的
I'll just edit that part out.
好的  很好
Oh, okay, good.
校内再次发现便便
变态屎犯大笔之作
变态屎犯作品:第二排第一个
瓦格斯塔夫小学地图  餐厅
音乐厅
该死  我们被别人捷"屎"先登了
Ah, damn it, we got poop-scooped!
每个人都在谈论蒂娜的报道
Tina's story is all anyone's talking about.
苔米  怎么搞的
Tammy, what happened?
你说要疯癫  不要便便啊
Well, you said gaga, not caca.
这个便便就很疯癫
This caca is gaga!
去给我挖它的新闻
Now get me that story.
怎么挖
I don't know how.
你不干我就让怪咖双胞胎换你
Do it, or I'll replace you with the weird twins.
话筒交还给你  安迪
Back to you, Andy!
话筒交还给你  奥利
Back to you, Ollie!
行了  停停停  当我没说
Whoa, okay, no, no, no! Forget it.
蒂娜  那个变态屎犯的报道不错嘛
Hey, Tina, great Mad Pooper reporting.
谢谢夸奖
Thanks.
我能抄不  就像我抄你的数学作业一样
Can I copy you like I do in math class?
做新闻和抄作业可不一样
Real news isn't about copying.
你也不该抄我的数学作业
And you shouldn't copy me in math.
我劝你找个家教
Yeah, well, you should get a tutor,
因为我得的是C
'cause I got a "C."
你得的C  等等  可我得的是D啊
You got a "C"? Wait, I got a "D."
不给抄算了  我自己去找
You know what? I'll do my own story.
肯定会比你的好上一百倍  笨蛋
And it'll be way better than yours, you lame-pon.
-很好  祝你成功  -必须的
- Good, I hope it is. - It will be.
因为这样一来
Because then we'll have more information
我就又多了一条变态屎犯的线索
about the Mad Pooper...
蒂娜  我跟你吵架呢
Tina, we're trash-talking; stop turning it into
别搞成好像在开国会一样
a normal conversation.
抱歉  烂货
Oh. Sorry. Um, skank?
好多了
That's much better!
你新发型真丑
Uh, I hate your new hair color.
继续
Give it to me!
你的眼影画得有点过了
Your eye shadow is a little much.
还不够  再猛一点
In the face! My face!
大事件
今日头条  蒂娜就是变态屎犯吗
Our top story: is Tina the Mad Pooper?
如果监控录像拍到了蒂娜的作案证据
What if actual surveillance footage existed
你会怎么看呢
showing Tina in the act?
我们根据监控录像拍到的内容
Let's go to a reenactment of what that footage
为大家模拟重现了当时的场景
might look like.
她总这么安静
She was always so quiet.
对  她都把自己封闭起来
Yeah, she kept to herself.
-确实如此  -确实如此
- Yeah, she did. - She did.
那么  这一切是否是蒂娜一手策划的呢
So, did Tina create the very story she reported on?
我们请到了格兰特先生谈谈他的看法
Mr. Grant is here to comment.
老实说  蒂娜来面试的时候
When Tina auditioned, frankly,
她的野心让我感到了身心的威胁
I was physically afraid of her ambition.
为了上电视  她可以不择手段
She would've done anything to get on TV.
很明显  目前看来  她确实这么做了
And now, apparently, she has.
我们还有蒂娜亲口承认起罪行的独家视频
Ah. And what if WSN had an exclusive video confession?
我  蒂娜  是  变态屎犯
Me-- Tina-- are-- Mad-- Pooper.
你们不会因为电视上那么说
You don't believe that
就真的相信吧
just because it was on TV, right?
明白  蒂娜
Got it. Tina?
去校长办公室  马上
Principal's office, now.
不是我干的
I didn't do it.
追踪"屎"迹
Follow the money.
此处借用水门事件中的经典名言
前联邦调查局副局长费尔特对记者作出的
关键指示  "追踪钱迹"
我愿意接受便便检测器测试
I'll take a poop detector test.
泄我一次  其错在你
Poop on me once, shame on you.
泄我两次  我们不再是挚友
Poop on me twice, we're not best friends anymore!
瓦格斯塔夫小学
不是我  那只是个模拟的视频
It's not me, it was a reenactment.
若非真的发生过  他们又怎么模拟呢
If it didn't happen, then how could they reenact it?
也是哦
Huh. Uh, yeah.
当秘书真是屈才了  你该去当老师
You should be a teacher instead of secretary, Ms. Schnur.
我一直这么觉得
I know.
露易丝  你来这儿干嘛
Louise, why are you here?
苔米没陷害你啊
Tammy didn't frame you.
我犯了别的事儿
Unrelated charge.
咨询顾问室  福旺德
好戏即将上演
And now we wait.
至少你是犯了事儿
At least you're guilty of something.
我是被陷害的
I got framed.
等斯普尔斯校长从禁烟大会回来
Cry to Principal Spoors when he gets back
跟他哭去吧
from the anti-smoking assembly.
天哪  禁烟大会
Oh, my God, the assembly!
全校都会参加
The whole school is there.
你还能想到比那儿更好的
Can you think of a better place
变态屎犯作案地点吗
for the Mad Pooper to strike?
超级碗  美国偶像
The Super Bowl, American Idol,
西敏寺犬展  上下颠倒的过山车
Westminster Dog Show, upside-down roller coaster,
国际空间站
International Space Station,
瑜伽静修  藏匿于衣内的手枪
yoga retreat, inside a T-shirt gun...
如果我能从这儿出去的话
If I could just get out of here,
我就能洗清罪名了
I could clear my name.
我来搞定舒娜老师
I'll take care of Ms. Schnur.
天  快看  有人在往一辆
Oh, no, look, they're towing a high-mileage, smallish car
高里程小轿车上贴车贴
with a bumper sticker
内容貌似是有关某人的个人爱好
about a personal passion maybe?
"我的另一辆车是只猫"
"My other car's a cat"?
没错
That's the one!
不
No!
但愿舒娜老师的车没事
I hope Ms. Schnur's car's okay.
快跑  蒂娜
Go, Tina!
哦  好的
Oh, yeah.
困境  罪恶的香烟
禁烟大会
姑娘  别告诉我你又犯事儿了
All right, missy, this better be good.
露易丝  你姐姐呢
Louise, where's your sister?
-蒂娜没在  吉恩  -别跟我顶嘴
- Tina's not here, Gene. - Don't you sass me!
我都不让老爸那样跟我讲话
Hey, I don't even let Dad talk to me like that.
我们尽快赶来了
We got here as soon as we could.
吉恩  你来这儿干嘛
Gene, what are you doing here?
-学校叫我来的  -不  叫的是我
- They called me! - No, they called me.
真不敢相信我女儿居然就是"屎男仆"
I can't believe my daughter is the Butt-ler.
我没有这个女儿
I have no daughter!
别那样讲  吉恩
Oh, don't say that, Gene.
对  他说得没错
Yes, he should say that.
走吧  她去禁烟大会
Come on, she's down at the assembly
洗清罪名去了
trying to clear her name.
这些小屁孩出生前我们的生活要轻松许多
Our lives were so much simpler before the rug rats.
我们那时还去看电影
We use to see movies...
琳
Lin!
对不起嘛  但他说得很对啊
Sorry, but it's true.
香烟是真正的恶魔
Cigarettes are the real devil sticks.
尼古丁百害而无一益
Nicotine is a bad scene.
我知道你在这儿  变态屎犯
You're here somewhere, Mad Pooper.
注意力集中点  我们一定要找到蒂...
Let's stay focused; we got to find Tin...
杂技表演诶
Ooh, jugglers!
能借下火吗
Hey, can I get a light?
当然  有烟堪抽直须抽嘛
Sure, smoke 'em if you got 'em.
这表演传达的信息真诡异
This is kind of a weird message.
我都想来只香烟了
I really want a cigarette.
我都想去耍杂技了
I really want to juggle.
-没找到线索吗  -没有
- No sign? - Nothing.
我的天  快看  是变态屎犯
Oh, my God, look. The Pooper.
我得上去才行  但要怎么上去呢
I need to get up there. But how?
你可以用那边那个液压式杠杆升降机
You could use that hydraulic scissor lift.
太棒了  我上去跟踪他
Perfect. I'll sneak up on him.
我会让动作轻得像只老鼠
I'll be as quiet as a mouse.
凯丽・玛希斯和乔丝玲戴的一样的发圈
Kelly Mathis and Jocelyn are wearing the same scrunchie.
但很明显乔丝铃戴着更好看
But Jocelyn is definitely wearing it better.
格兰特老师  看哪
Mr. Grant, look.
是蒂娜
It's Tina.
她在那上面干嘛
What's she doing up there?
或许她真的就是变态屎犯
Maybe she is the Mad Pooper.
搞不好我们没自己想得那么邪恶
Hey, we're better than we thought.
去拿摄像机
Let's get that camera.
很好  来抓她个现行
Yeah, catch her in the act.
还就在大舞台上
On the big screen!
这新闻真实太劲爆了
That's a big load of news.
看哪  各位
Look, everyone!
是变态屎犯
It's the Mad Pooper!
是蒂娜
Ah, it's Tina!
蒂娜  你在干嘛  快下来
Tina, what are you doing? Get down!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
别躲在暗处了  变态屎犯
Come out of the shadows, Mad Pooper.
-齐克  -没想到吧
- Zeke? - Surprised?
齐克才是屎男仆
Zeke's the Butt-ler!
你为什么要这么做  齐克
Why'd you do it, Zeke?
第一次其实只是意外
Well, the first time was an accident.
但第二次就是好玩儿了
But the second time was for fun.
接着是意外  好玩儿  好玩儿
Then accident, fun, fun,
又是意外  然后连续三次都是好玩儿
another accident, three funs in a row,
到后来  我完全是做给你看了  蒂娜
then after that, I was doing it for you, Tina.
不过现在一切都结束了
But now it's over.
还没结束
It's not over.
-我还有一泡  -齐克  别这样
- I got one left! - Zeke, no.
拉  拉  拉
Poop! Poop! Poop!
拉  拉  拉  拉  拉
Poop! Poop! Poop! Poop! Poop!
笨蛋  听听你们都在说什么
Stupid kids, listen to them.
拉屎一点都不好玩儿
Poop's not funny.
好吧  有一点好玩  但是我想说的是
I mean, it is a little, but what sort of message are we--
我受不了了  我想看他拉屎
I can't stand it! I want to see him poop!
我想做回小孩儿
I want to be a kid again!
拉  拉  拉
Poop! Poop! Poop!
谢天谢地  他终于正常了
Oh, thank God. He's back.
我会想念翻版小鲍鲍的
Aw, I'll miss my Muppet Baby Bobby.
你不必这么做的
You don't have to do this.
拉  拉  拉  拉
Poop! Poop! Poop! Poop!
来了
Here we go.
这次不是意外
This isn't an accident!
不对  是意外  是意外
No, it is, it is.
天  我去
Oh, God. Oh, boy.
好慢啊
It's taking a long time.
是女孩儿
It's a girl!
不对  是男孩儿
Uh, no, it's a boy!
我们这看的都是啥呀
I guess we're really watching this.
鲍鲍  快握住我的手
Bobby, hold my hand.
快给我出来
Get out of there!
不
No!
苔米  小心
Tammy, look out!
不
No...!
今日头条  变态屎犯差点唬弄了我
Our top story: the Mad Pooper almost nails me.
今天来到演播室的是拯救了我头发的女生
I'm joined by the girl who saved my hair.
露易丝  当时可真悬
Louise, it was so close.
老实说  苔米
I thought it was going to be
我本来还想让它更悬一点的
a lot closer, Tammy, to be honest.
可惜我计算失误了
But I miscalculated.
也许是风力干扰
Wind, maybe.
我还以为屎会直接掉我嘴里呢  吓死了
I was scared there was gonna be poop right into my mouth.
下面让我们去看看变态屎犯本人齐克
Let's go to the Mad Pooper himself, Zeke,
令人费解的是  他居然没被定罪
who, incredibly, is not in trouble.
让我们来看看其中缘由
Let's find out why.
我家经常搬来搬去
My family moves around a lot.
他家经常搬来搬去
His family moves around a lot.
瓦格斯塔夫校园新闻台在此就之前无意中
Uh, WSN would like to apologize for any inadvertent suggestion
暗示蒂娜是屎犯道歉  是我们的错
that Tina Belcher was the Mad Pooper. Our bad.
下面为各位推出我台新栏目  蒂娜视角
And now, a new WSN feature: The Tina Table.
学校是否正逐渐升温
Is it getting hot in here?
一项调查显示  校护士的温度计
One study shows the school nurse's thermometer
平均下降了一度
is off by one degree.
我们把她请到了演播室
She's here to discuss it.
之后我们会就午餐零食交易一事采访学生
Later, I'll talk to students about trading snacks at lunch.
这是内线交易吗
Is it insider trading?
事实并非如此
No, it isn't.
看看我家的女主播
Look at my news girl,
那颗漂亮的脑袋像气球一样浮在空中
her pretty head floating like a balloon.
我感觉没躯干的蒂娜看着更顺眼
Is it just me,
是只有我这么想吗
or does Tina look great without a torso?
真想看看她蓄上胡子再秃个顶是啥样
Wonder how'd she look with a mustache and a bald spot?
我记起西班牙海鲜饭的做法了
Oh, I just remembered how to make paella.